Hello.
こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
Somewhat.
若干
I am doing?
してます?
I've been doing it for a while.
ちょっとしてますね
Thank you for coming today.
今日来てくださってありがとうございます
Sorry for being late.
遅れちゃってすいません
It's totally fine.
全然大丈夫です
It's very beautiful.
すごくきれいですね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's true.
本当です
marry me.
結婚してください
terrible.
やばい
It was a physical disability.
体障害でしたね
Wow, your feet are beautiful too.
すごい、足もきれいで
Can I wait a moment?
ちょっと待っていいです?
I usually start slower, but
いつもはもっとゆっくり始めるんですけど、
I don't have much time, so please take a look here.
時間が全然ないので、 こっち見てください
What kind of life should I lead, what kind of benefits should I accumulate, such a cute face?
どういう人生を送ったら、どんな得を積んだら そんなかわいい顔
Can you become one?
にな れるの?
Is it cute?
かわいいですか?
If you ask me if I'm cute or pretty,
かわいいか、きれいかって言われたら、
Which one is better?
どっちのほうがいいの?
I might be happy with both.
どちらも嬉しいかも
yes?
そう?
It's cute and beautiful.
かわいいし、きれいですよ
Are you in need of money?
お金困ってるんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
That's right.
ですよね
Please provide your name and age.
お名前と年齢をお願いします
With full name.
フルネームで
Please don't use your real name.
本名はやめてくださいね
Probably, nicknames often used by friends are not good either.
たぶんね、よくお友達とかに言われる ニックネームもよくない
Yes, it is.
んです よ
Yes, they look alike from generation to generation.
そうだね、代々似てるとか
If we look alike, we are said to look alike,
似てるのは、 似てるって言われるの、
Like Masaka Tsubasa.
マスアカ・ツバサとか
That's right.
そうだわ
Yes, that's true.
そうだわ、確かに
Someone told me I looked like him.
誰かに似てるって言われて
This is Tsubasa Masaka.
マスアカ・ツバサだ
Are you conscious?
意識してます?
I haven't.
してないです
Aren't you conscious of your hairstyle?
髪型とか意識してるんじゃないの?
yes.
そう
Then, is Tsubasa-chan okay?
じゃあ、ツバサちゃんでいいですか?
19 years old.
19歳
I can't drink alcohol yet.
まだお酒飲めないね
I can't drink it.
飲めないです
I haven't been drinking.
飲んでないね
Even in my 20s, I don't have any money.
20代もお金ないんですよ
Kids in their 20s today don't have much money.
今日20代の子達ってお金ないんですよ
I don't think there are any more 19 year olds.
19歳はもっとないと思いますよ
No, not at all.
ないです、全然
The current Liberal Democratic Party is bad.
今の自民党が悪いね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Do you know what we're going to do today?
今日何するかって知ってますか?
roughly.
大体
good.
よかった
If you don't know anything about it, you'll get caught with a steadfast certificate of success.
全く知らないんだったら、 不動意成功証で捕まっちゃうんだよ
It's okay there.
そこは大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
What are you doing today?
何するんですか、今日?
Naughty things.
エッチなこと
I'll take a picture of it with a camera and show it to the whole world,
それをカメラで撮って、 全世界に公開しちゃいますけど、
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
That's terrible.
やばいですね
Should I stop?
やめとく?
Don't do it at all.
全然やめて
sorry.
すみません
Our work is AV advancement, so
我 々の仕事はAV進歩っていうので、
It's very strictly restricted.
すごく厳しく制限されておりますので
If something happens that I don't like at all, can I go home?
全然嫌なことあったら帰っていい?
It's okay.
大丈夫ですからね
There's no such thing as compulsion.
強制とかはないので
Is it okay to have sex with an uncle?
おじさんとのエッチ大丈夫?
It's totally okay.
全然大丈夫
Is everything okay?
全然大丈夫?
I like older people.
年上好きなんで
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Because I'm not too old.
年上すぎないから
not at all.
全然
It's going to be hot right away, so let's take it off at the top.
早速熱いので、 上で脱いでいきましょうね
Are you wearing heattech?
ヒートテック着てるの?
It was hot.
熱かったです
HEATTECH is still too hot this season, isn't it?
今の季節、ヒートテックまだ熱すぎでしょ?
Are you sensitive to cold?
寒がりなの?
I'm a little cold.
ちょっと寒がり
I think we still have a long way to go.
まだまだ全然先だと思うよ
It was cold in the morning.
朝寒かった
It's cold in the morning, but it's starting to get cold,
朝寒いけど、 寒くなりだすけど、
Isn't it still too early for that?
まだそれも早いんじゃない?
Yes, yes.
そう ね、はい
Please fall asleep underneath too.
下も寝いちゃってください
Do you like blue?
青好きなの?
I like it.
好きですね
light blue.
水色
Do you like light blue?
水色好き?
spider
クモ
mosquito.
か
With a 4K camera.
4K カメラで
Can I stare at you?
ジロジロとっちゃっていい?
Yeah.
うん
I might get a little angry, but
ちょっと怒っちゃうかもしれないけど、
My pants are fraying a lot.
パンツがなんかほつれが多いね
It's true.
本当だ
Don't have money to buy underwear?
下着買うお金ないの?
do not have.
ない
Because I always wear the same one.
同じのばっか着てるから
Is that so?
そう なの?
With heattech.
ヒートテックで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I need help with this.
これは助けてあげないとね
Oh my god.
おへっそう
Shine your hair.
髪の毛をシャインして
Please wear a nice necklace.
ネックレスいいのつけてよね
I'm spending money on things like this.
こういうのにお金使っちゃうの
As a reward.
ご褒美で
Sometimes sometimes.
たまにたまに
It's a reward.
ご褒美です
What is it?
なんだね
So why don't you take a picture of your bra?
じゃあ、ブラジャー撮ってごらん?
Hello.
こんにちは
こんにちはしちゃって
Hello.
Is it difficult?
難しいの?
It's difficult.
難しいです
It's okay to be dignified.
堂々としていいんだよ
There are hundreds of naked men waiting behind this camera.
このカメラの向こうに 何百人って男が 裸で待機してるんで、
Everyone is looking at Tsubasa-chan.
全員が ツバサちゃんを見てます
Say hello.
こんにちはって挨拶して
Hello.
こんにちは
Would you like to shake my hand?
手を振ってごらん?
nice.
いいね
Can I lick your cock?
コッパイ舐めちゃってもいいですか?
May I?
いい ですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
yes?
そう?
Please sit down.
座ってください
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
While we meet together.
一緒にお会いしながら
While meeting with me.
私とお会いしながら
I just ran away and left you alone.
さっき逃げちゃって、 お手垂らしちゃいました
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
ERROR
汗くさいかも
I don't have any strings attached.
ひもくせいのあったしません
What was your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何だった?
yogurt.
ヨーグルト
yogurt?
ヨーグルト?
Do you like yogurt?
ヨーグルト好きなの?
I like yogurt.
ヨーグルト好き
What's good?
何がいいの?
Of yogurt?
ヨーグルトの?
Yeah.
うん
ERROR
体にいいし
Yeah.
うん
It's probably good day or night.
日でも夜も多分いいし
I'm careful about my health.
健康には気を使っているんだ
ERROR
健康も
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I'm really nervous.
めっちゃ緊張してるの
It's Itotek.
イトテックだね
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
ERROR
鼓動がすごい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm embarrassed to see myself on camera.
カメラに映る自分、恥ずかしい
Ah so
あ そ
This is delicious.
こ おいしい
I put both hands behind my head.
両手は頭の後ろに持ってきたから
Rounded sides.
脇が丸み
Look here.
こっち見て
Open it and take it down.
開いて下ろして
Can I open it and take it down?
開いて下ろしていい?
There might be some.
ちょっとあるかも
Don't hide it, don't hide it.
隠しちゃダメ、隠しちゃダメ
Hide it.
隠すの
I'll do it here with mosaic.
モザイクでこっちでやるんで
It's okay.
大丈夫ですよ
Oh, it's so delicious.
あ、すごいおいしい
Aren't you sweating?
汗かいてません?
sweat?
汗?
It tastes great and is salty.
すごい味ししょっぱいです
Show me your left hand.
左手見せて
Ah, this one isn't growing.
あ、こっちは生えてない
Come here.
こっちきて
Open the licking light and show me.
舐めライト開き見せてごらん
Carefully bring it back to the back of your head.
上手にまた頭の後ろに持ってきて
You got licked.
舐められちゃったね
You don't have to wash it.
洗わなくていいよ
Because it's beautiful there.
そこきれいだから
So, how can I sit on this sofa?
じゃあ、このソファーで こうやって座れる?
I want you to sit here.
ここ座ってほしいよ
Do you understand?
わかるかな?
My butt.
お尻が
Tsubasa's butt.
つばさちゃんのお尻が
Is your butt hole here?
お尻の穴ここ?
Does it match?
合ってる?
Is your butt hole here?
お尻の穴ここ?
Okay, now sit like this.
じゃあ、今度は こうやって座ってごらん
Is your butt hole here?
お尻の穴ここ?
Yeah.
うん
Is your butt hole here?
お尻の穴ここ?
Uncle, I'm good at hitting buttholes.
おじさん、お尻の穴あてるの得意なんです
So, can I take it off?
じゃあ、脱がしていい?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
It's totally fine.
全然大丈夫ですよ
Take it off.
脱がしてね
It doesn't have a butt hole at all.
全然お尻の穴とかついてないよ
It's totally okay
全然大丈夫です
Yo.
よ
Butt and pants.
お 尻とパンツ
It's not attached to the butt side, but it's attached to the pussy side.
お尻側にはついてないけど、 おまんこ側はついてる
What is this?
何これ?
No way.
やだー
Oh, wait.
え、待って
Look this way?
こっち向いてごらん?
Stand normally.
普通に立って
I said something like this.
こんなのするとた
Were you walking around so tight?
こんな締め付けて歩いてたの?
Sorry.
すいません
Why don't you say that?
って言ってごらん?
Sorry.
すいません
I'll give it back to you.
お返しします
I can't go home wearing those clothes.
それおじさん履いて帰れないから
Well then, you can leave it as normal.
じゃあ、普通に置いていいよ
Well then, let's just sit down normally.
じゃあ、普通に一回座ろうか
sorry.
ご めんなさい
Sit down once.
一回座って
This is how the legs are made.
足がこうできる
So stand up, stand up.
じゃあ、立って立って
join hands together.
一緒に手を組んで
Kurosuke.
黒くろすけ
There is a black Kurosuke.
黒くろすけがいる
Is it warped around here?
ここら辺は反ってるんだ?
Did you leave just a little bit here?
ここだけちょい残したの?
Do you want to hide it?
隠したいの?
Is that so?
そうなの?
As much as possible.
なるべくですね
Don't put your hand in front of your pussy.
おまんこの前に手を持ってかないように
Mosaic would be difficult.
モザイクが大変だっちゃうね
So, can you spread your legs?
じゃあ、足広げれる?
Let's take a look.
覗いちゃおう
Do you have any plans to get your hair removed?
脱毛する予定とかあるの?
Well, maybe not now.
いや、今はないかな
do not have?
ない?
It's important to buy pants.
パンツを買うことが大事だね
You can buy it, with today's money.
買えますよ、今日のお金で
Can you change your image in front of the sofa?
ソファーの前でイメージ改革できる?
Do you understand image reform?
イメージ改革って分かる?
I understand.
分かります
Where did you study?
どこで学んだの?
Isn't that quite the case?
結構あれじゃないですか
Isn't it famous?
有名じゃないですか
Keep your hands at your sides.
手は横にして
Tsubasa-san.
つばささん
Why is it white?
なんで白いの?
Is it white?
白いですかね?
white.
白い
Tsubasa-chan's spread is big.
つばさちゃんのビラビラが大きいね
The lid is ready.
蓋ができてる
Can it be expanded?
広げれる?
Well then, thank you for your help today.
じゃあ、今日はよろしくお願いしますね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm going home.
帰ります
Are you going home?
帰る?
I'm not going home.
帰んない
Help your hair.
髪の毛を支援して
You can hide it.
隠していいよ
I hid it.
隠したやん
Place your hands behind your head.
両手は頭の後ろに待ってきて
I'm lying down, so put your head there.
横になってるから、そっちに頭を置いて
On your back?
仰向け?
start?
スタート?
Is your body warm?
体が温まった?
It warmed me up.
温まった
It's warm.
温まったね
Drink butter cookies.
バタークッキーを飲むの
why?
なんで?
Did you put something in it?
何か入れた?
sweet.
甘い
Do you like being eaten?
食べられるの好きなの?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
It's getting really big.
すごく大きくなってる
Is it cool?
涼しいですか?
Tsubasa's pussy.
つばさちゃんのおまんこ
eat?
食べる?
It's hot.
暑いね
暑 いね
It looks like it's going to fly away.
飛んできそう
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
This can also be a burden.
これ と負担もできる
I can also bear the burden.
負担もできる
I'll eat it.
食べるよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
There are traces of mucus flying around.
粘 液が飛ぶ跡が出てるんだけど
Did it feel good?
気 持ちよかったの?
Can you see the mucus?
粘液映るかな?
Tsubasa liquid.
つばさ液
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Tsubasa-chan's membrane is cracked at the bottom.
つばさちゃんの所属膜は、下が割れてるんだね
Is that so?
そうなの?
It hurt a lot at first.
最初はすごく痛かったね
The entrance is narrow.
入れ口狭い
Wasn't it really painful for the first time?
初めてすごく痛くなかった?
No, it didn't hurt that much.
いや、そんなに痛くなかった
The membrane here is torn and it hurts.
ここ膜が破れちゃって痛いんだけど
The first person breaks through the bottom.
最初の人が下を突き破ってますね
The ore that the first person broke through is etched into Tsubasa's body.
最初の人が突き破った鉱石が、 つばさちゃんの体に刻み込ま
It is.
れて
Do you think it's mysterious?
神 秘的だと思う?
Yeah.
うん
The first person's ore.
最初の人の鉱石が
How many cup breasts do you have now?
おっぱい今何カップあるの?
D cup.
Dカップ
Are you satisfied?
満足してる?
I haven't.
してない
Did you want more?
もっと欲しかったの?
How much did you want it?
どれくらい欲しかったの?
About E.
Eくらい
Current moa size?
今のモアサイズ?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Do you want to hide your pussy?
おまんこ隠したいの?
Just a little more.
もう ちょっと
Should I keep my hands behind my back?
手を後ろに置いておくのかな?
is that so.
そうですか
When did the black pie start getting bigger?
いつくらいクロッパイ大きくなり始めたの?
Like going up and down?
昇降とか?
It was early.
早かったんだ
Did it stop there?
そ こで止まっちゃったの?
It hasn't stopped.
止まってはないよね
It may still be going on.
まだ続いてるかもしれない
It's totally okay.
全然大丈夫
It's been 100 years.
100年になった
With the rest of my life.
余生と
Very easy to pick up.
すごいつまみやすい
hard?
硬い?
yes.
そう
It is said that the shape is beautiful.
形は綺麗って言われる
Although it's small.
小さいけど
Shape of bloat?
うっぱいの形?
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Her body is beautiful.
体が綺麗です
I made Kachan.
かちゃん作った
I have to make a bonus with this.
これでボニュー作らないと
I really hate it.
すごい大嫌い
Lick my nice face.
いい顔舐めて
Please open it.
開 いてね
Get it all together.
そろしてもらう
Can I sleep?
寝ていい?
good.
いい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Go to sleep.
寝てよ
Please spread your legs.
足元広げてください
Please hold me.
抱えてください
Put your hands behind your back.
手を後ろに置いて
I'm sleeping over there.
あそこに寝てる
Fold your legs.
足たたんで
oh yeah.
そうそう
So and then.
それでそして
It suddenly went into night mode.
急にナイトモードになった
Please bring it.
持ってきてください
Fold your legs.
足たたんで
Please bring it.
持 ってきてください
Fall down here
こっちに倒れてきて
please.
ください
Please sleep.
寝 てください
Put your head on the bed.
頭はベッドにつけて
You have hair up to your butt.
お尻まで毛があるんだね
Use both hands to open your butthole.
両手でお尻の穴を開けてください
oh yeah.
そうそう
Do you want me to say more dick?
もっとチンコ言ってほしい?
Both hands are closed.
両手が閉まってる
Which is better, Cheap or Drama Cheap?
チープとドラマチープはどっちがいいの?
Do you want to be taken inside?
中に出されたいの?
Do you like holes in the inside and legs?
中と足の穴が好きなの?
like.
好き
Is that why you have a hobby downstairs?
だから下での趣味なの?
It's not a hobby though.
趣味だないけど
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Please tell me to prepare as much as possible.
私でいっぱい仕込んでくださいって言ってください
Please make me a jewelery sporter.
私でいっぱ jewelseryスポーターでください
Please make sure to show me how you are being placed by your uncle.
おじさんに置かされている姿をもいっぱい仕込まれてくださいって
Do you want me to say it?
言 ってほしいですか
Please show me a lot of images of being placed in the hands of an old man.
おじさんに置かされている姿をいっぱい仕込まれてください
Let's get my head down again.
もう一回首いってもらおう
I'll ask you to give me as much as you can.
いっぱい出してくださいって言ってもらおう
Let me tell you that I like being friends with you.
仲良しされるの好きなのって言ってもらおう
I like being made friends.
仲良しされるの好き
Let me hold your legs in your hands
手で両足抱えてもらお
cormorant.
う
Have them apply pressure while pushing.
押 しながらキュッキュッと力を入れてもらおう
Can I make it normal?
普通にしていい?
Expand the mark?
マーク広げる?
Your nails are long.
爪長いね
Please look here.
こっち見てください
Did you feel sick?
気持ち悪かった?
So let's have Mark do it first.
だから最初はマークやってもらおう
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
See you soon, bye.
またね、バイバイ
Now, press the foot that can see the mark clearly.
じゃあ、マークをよく見える足を押して、
Shall we go out?
出てみようか
It's left behind.
残っちゃったですね
You don't have to cut it out, just slide it in and out.
抜き切らなくていいから、下に出し入れして
That's it.
そういうことです
Put it under
下に入れて、
Put it on top.
上 に入れて
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
amazing.
すごい
Are there that many?
そんなにあるの?
interesting.
面白い
So let's include that as well.
じゃあ、それも入れてみようか
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Don't hide it too much.
あまり隠さないで
Pretty clear.
結構鮮明
It looks really close up.
めっちゃアップに見えますね
Put it in and take it out.
出し入れして
Shall I try to get some sleep?
ゆっくり寝てみようか
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
It's cute.
かわいいよ
Let's press the foot that can clearly see the mark and try to get out.
マークをよく見える足を押して、 出てみようか
It's left behind.
残っちゃったですね
You don't have to cut it out, just slide it in and out.
抜き切らなくていいから、下に出し入れして
That's it.
そういうことです
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
amazing.
すごい
Don't hide it too much.
あまり隠さないで
Is there such a thing?
そんな にあるの?
interesting.
面白い
So let's include that as well.
じゃあ、それも入れてみようか
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Don't hide it too much.
あまり隠さないで
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Pretty clear.
結構鮮明
It looks really close up.
めっちゃアップに見えますね
Put it in and take it out.
出し入れして
Shall I try to get some sleep?
ゆっくり寝てみようか
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました